

PROFILE

Born in Cyprus, 20 years old computer enthusiast. Programming and Game Development with experience from the age of 13. Worked in a company and designed a professional website in the age of 15. Active person with passion in Drumming and Music. Fluent in Greek and English, very skilled on communicating and developing relationships in workplace. My goal is to work in huge projects in big companies and create life-changing video games.

CONTACT

PHONE: +35799920132

EMAIL: Kouis16cy@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Drumming
Gaming
Game Development
Video Editing

NIKOLAOS KOUIS

EDUCATION

LINOPETRA LYCEUM

2016 - 2019

Field of Physical Sciences and Computer Science

Essex University

2020 -

Undergraduate of BSc Computer Science, Year 2.

WORK EXPERIENCE

QS Lysis - Web Designer

2016-2018

Designer the Official and Professional Website of the company.

KIK Trading – Mini Mall Stores (MMS)

2021-2021

Summer job as a cashier in MMS in Limassol.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Pancyprian Discus Throwing Competition Participant
- Grade 7 of Drumming
- Duke of Edinburgh's International Award Bronze Course
- Computer IGCSEs Mathematics IGCSEs First Language Pearson Edexcel - Second Language Cambridge
- Unity Unreal Engine Projects
- Website Designer
- The Loop: Ouroboros, Horror Game, currently on Alpha.
- Ritualist, Horror Game, currently on Alpha.
- Joined the Global Game Jam 2022, Horror game on Unity, Finished.